(Penny:)Is he quitting his job
at the university?
Oh, no. He's gonna telecommute.
(Leonard:)Everybody's really excited about it.
(Sheldon:)All right. Boone, North Carolina.
"Every summer since 1952,
Boone has hosted...
(Sheldon:)...an outdoor amphitheater portrayal
of the life and times...
...of its namesake: Danel Boone."
That sounds like something
that would attract the wrong crowd.
(Sheldon:)-Penny, you're from Nebraska, correct?
-Born and raised.
(Sheldon:)It will take me a few days to get settled.
After I do, I will e-mail you...
(Sheldon:)...detailed PDFs containing diagrams
and instructions...
(Sheldon:)...that will guide you through packing
and shipping my possessions...
(Sheldon:)...to Bozeman, Montana.
(Sheldon:)In the meantime,
please forward my mail.
Anyplace specific, or just
the Bozeman, Montana loony bin?